[{
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What movie was directed by Mike Newell in 1994?",
    "options": [
    { "id": "A", "text": "Four Weddings and a Funeral" },
    { "id": "B", "text": "The Belles of St Trinian's" },
    { "id": "C", "text": "Don't Look Now" },
    { "id": "D", "text": "The 39 Steps" }
    ],
    "answer": "A"
    },
    {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What is the name of the first major railway built in Britain?",
    "options": [
    { "id": "A", "text": "Eastern Railway" },
    { "id": "B", "text": "Eurostar" },
    { "id": "C", "text": "Great Western Railway" },
    { "id": "D", "text": "High Speed" }
    ],
    "answer": "C"
    },
    {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "UK residents should register their car or motorcycle at:",
    "options": [
    { "id": "A", "text": "The Ministry of Transport (MOT)" },
    { "id": "B", "text": "The Local Police Office" },
    { "id": "C", "text": "The petrol station" },
    { "id": "D", "text": "The Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency (DVLA)" }
    ],
    "answer": "D"
    },
    {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What are trade unions?",
    "options": [
    { "id": "A", "text": "Associations that support each other and work together towards shared goals in democracy" },
    { "id": "B", "text": "Associations that support each other and work together towards shared goals in development" },
    { "id": "C", "text": "Organizations that aim to improve the pay and working conditions of their members" },
    { "id": "D", "text": "Organizations responsible for the protection and promotion of human rights" }
    ],
    "answer": "C"
    },
    {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "Who were the Huguenots?",
    "options": [
    { "id": "A", "text": "Refugees from France" },
    { "id": "B", "text": "Refugees from Italy" },
    { "id": "C", "text": "Refugees from Pakistan" },
    { "id": "D", "text": "Refugees from Cyprus" }
    ],
    "answer": "A"
    },
    {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "Where do the Welsh Assembly Members meet?",
    "options": [
    { "id": "A", "text": "Stormont" },
    { "id": "B", "text": "Westminster" },
    { "id": "C", "text": "Holyrood" },
    { "id": "D", "text": "Senedd" }
    ],
    "answer": "D"
    },
    {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "What British scientist showed who gravity applied to the whole universe?",
    "options": [
    { "id": "A", "text": "Alan Turing" },
    { "id": "B", "text": "Alexander Fleming" },
    { "id": "C", "text": "Isaac Newton" },
    { "id": "D", "text": "Ernest Rutherford" }
    ],
    "answer": "C"
    },
    {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "Who was Elizabeth I's mother?",
    "options": [
    { "id": "A", "text": "Catherine Howard" },
    { "id": "B", "text": "Anne Boleyn" },
    { "id": "C", "text": "Catherine Parr" },
    { "id": "D", "text": "Catherine of Aragon" }
    ],
    "answer": "B"
    },
    {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "What composer wrote music for King George I and for his son, George II?",
    "options": [
    { "id": "A", "text": "George Frederick Handel" },
    { "id": "B", "text": "Gustav Holst" },
    { "id": "C", "text": "Ralph Vaughan Williams" },
    { "id": "D", "text": "Henry Purcell" }
    ],
    "answer": "A"
    },
    {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Which of the following is the responsibility of the Foreign Secretary?",
    "options": [
    { "id": "A", "text": "Economy" },
    { "id": "B", "text": "Education and health" },
    { "id": "C", "text": "Managing relationships with foreign countries" },
    { "id": "D", "text": "Crime, policing and immigration" }
    ],
    "answer": "C"
    },
    {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "A popular way for people to stay in touch with friends, organise social events, and share photos, videos and opinions is through social networking websites such as:",
    "options": [
    { "id": "A", "text": "Dropbox and iTunes" },
    { "id": "B", "text": "Email and Fax" },
    { "id": "C", "text": "eBay and Amazon" },
    { "id": "D", "text": "Facebook and Twitter" }
    ],
    "answer": "D"
    },
    {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "What sort of battle was 'the Battle of Britain'?",
    "options": [
    { "id": "A", "text": "A naval battle against the French" },
    { "id": "B", "text": "An aerial battle against the Germans" },
    { "id": "C", "text": "An aerial battle against the French" },
    { "id": "D", "text": "A naval battle against the Spanish" }
    ],
    "answer": "B"
    },
    {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "Why is it important to recycle (select two answers)?",
    "options": [
    { "id": "A", "text": "It is a criminal offence and you could be arrested if you do not do it" },
    { "id": "B", "text": "The Mousetrap is an environmental policy aiming to prevent mice from destroying crops" },
    { "id": "C", "text": "To reduce the expenses of the local council" },
    { "id": "D", "text": "Less rubbish is created, so the amount being put into landfill is reduced" }
    ],
    "answer": ["A", "D"]
    },
    {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "When is the birth of Jesus Christ celebrated?",
    "options": [
    { "id": "A", "text": "24th December" },
    { "id": "B", "text": "25th December" },
    { "id": "C", "text": "26th December" },
    { "id": "D", "text": "31st December" }
    ],
    "answer": "B"
    },
    {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "What is the area covered by Loch Lomond and the Trossachs National Park?",
    "options": [
    { "id": "A", "text": "720 square miles" },
    { "id": "B", "text": "840 square miles" },
    { "id": "C", "text": "620 square miles" },
    { "id": "D", "text": "940 square miles" }
    ],
    "answer": "A"
    },
    {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "In which city is the Millennium Stadium located?",
    "options": [
    { "id": "A", "text": "Birmingham" },
    { "id": "B", "text": "Nottingham" },
    { "id": "C", "text": "Liverpool" },
    { "id": "D", "text": "Cardiff" }
    ],
    "answer": "D"
    },
    {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "When was the first tennis club founded in the United Kingdom?",
    "options": [
    { "id": "A", "text": "1860" },
    { "id": "B", "text": "1872" },
    { "id": "C", "text": "1902" },
    { "id": "D", "text": "1892" }
    ],
    "answer": "B"
    },
    {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "What kind of sport is played at the Wimbledon Championships?",
    "options": [
    { "id": "A", "text": "Football" },
    { "id": "B", "text": "Tennis" },
    { "id": "C", "text": "Rugby" },
    { "id": "D", "text": "Cricket" }
    ],
    "answer": "B"
    },
    {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "Where is the MP's office situated?",
    "options": [
    { "id": "A", "text": "At the House of Commons" },
    { "id": "B", "text": "At Whitehall" },
    { "id": "C", "text": "At 10 Downing Street" },
    { "id": "D", "text": "At the House of Lords" }
    ],
    "answer": "A"
    },
    {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "Where was Isaac Newton from?",
    "options": [
    { "id": "A", "text": "Lincolnshire" },
    { "id": "B", "text": "Stratford-upon-Avon" },
    { "id": "C", "text": "Cardiff" },
    { "id": "D", "text": "Edinburgh" }
    ],
    "answer": "A"
    },
    {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "Is the statement below TRUE or FALSE? The Council of Europe has the power to make new laws.",
    "options": [
    { "id": "A", "text": "TRUE" },
    { "id": "B", "text": "FALSE" }
    ],
    "answer": "B"
    },
    {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "Which TWO British poets wrote about their experiences in WWI?",
    "options": [
    { "id": "A", "text": "Lord Byron and Percy Shelley" },
    { "id": "B", "text": "John Keats and Alfred Lord Tennyson" },
    { "id": "C", "text": "Robert and Elizabeth Browning" },
    { "id": "D", "text": "Wilfred Owen and Siegfried Sassoon" }
    ],
    "answer": "D"
    },
    {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "Is the statement below TRUE or FALSE? If you are facing domestic violence, you can phone the 24-hour National Domestic Violence Freephone Helpline, or the police can help you find a safe place to stay.",
    "options": [
    { "id": "A", "text": "TRUE" },
    { "id": "B", "text": "FALSE" }
    ],
    "answer": "A"
    },
    {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "If you are found driving while exceeding the alcohol limit, you will:",
    "options": [
    { "id": "A", "text": "Not be allowed to drive again" },
    { "id": "B", "text": "Be taken to the hospital" },
    { "id": "C", "text": "Be arrested" },
    { "id": "D", "text": "Be taken home by the police" }
    ],
    "answer": "C"
    }
]